Senate fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Senate Committees, 1965 - 1987; F-84-1; 13.72 m of textual records
  - Senate Library Committee (SLC), 1966 - 1981; F-84-1-5; 26 cm of textual records
    - SLC - papers 26-50, 1967; F-84-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1968; F-84-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - papers 51-75, 1968; F-84-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1969; F-84-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - papers 76-98, 1969; F-84-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1970; F-84-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - papers 99-119, 1970; F-84-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1971; F-84-1-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-24)
    - SLC - papers 120-150, 1971; F-84-1-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - index papers 151 to 78-22, F-84-1-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - agenda, minutes and Senate report, 1972; F-84-1-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - papers 151-175, 1972; F-84-1-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1973 - 1974; F-84-1-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - papers 74-1 to 74-5, 1973 - 1974; F-84-1-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1975 - 1976; F-84-1-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - papers 75-1 to 76-8, 1975 - 1976; F-84-1-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - agenda and minutes, 1977 - 1978; F-84-1-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - SLC - papers 77-1 to 78-22, 1977 - 1978; F-84-1-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - Senate Library Penalties Appeals -- terms of reference, 1971 - 1981; F-84-1-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - Senate Library Penalties Appeals -- reports, 1979 - 1980; F-84-1-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - Senate Library Penalties Appeals -- agenda and minutes, 1973 - 1979; F-84-1-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
    - Senate Library Penalties Appeals -- agenda and minutes, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-25)
  - Senate Undergraduate Appeals Board (SUAB), 1965 - 1978; F-84-1-6; 38 cm of textual records
    - SUAB - Admissions Committee, 1965 - 1966; F-84-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Apr. 11, 1966 - Dec. 28, 1967, 1966 - 1967; F-84-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. 12, 1968 - Dec. 1968, F-84-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - July 1969, F-84-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Aug. - Dec. 1969, F-84-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Oct. - Dec. 1971, 1970; F-84-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Sept. 1970, 1970 - 1971; F-84-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-26)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Dec. 1972, F-84-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-27)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Dec. 1973, F-84-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-27)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Dec. 1974, F-84-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-27)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Dec. 1975, F-84-1-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-27)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Dec. 1976, F-84-1-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-28)
      Open
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - Dec. 1977, F-84-1-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-28)
    - SUAB - additional minutes. Mar. - Nov. 1977, F-84-1-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-28)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. Jan. - May 1978, F-84-1-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-28)
    - SUAB - minutes and papers. June - Dec. 1978, F-84-1-6-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-28)
      Restrict in whole
  - Senate Committee on Academic Discipline (SCAD), 1971 - 1984; F-84-1-7; 38 cm of textual records
    - SCAD - confidential, F-84-1-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - cases -- L to Y, 1971 - 1979; F-84-1-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - cases -- L to W, 1978 - 1980; F-84-1-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - cases -- A to V, 1980 - 1981; F-84-1-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - correspondence and papers. Oct. 15, 1981, F-84-1-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - cases -- H to W, 1981 - 1982; F-84-1-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - cases -- G to W, 1981 - 1982; F-84-1-7-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-29)
    - SCAD - cases -- F to W, 1982; F-84-1-7-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - case -- T, 1982; F-84-1-7-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - cases -- F to T, 1982 - 1983; F-84-1-7-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - cases -- B to H, 1983 - 1984; F-84-1-7-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - cases -- B to R, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - cases -- O, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - cases -- C to P, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-30)
    - SCAD - case -- H, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-31)
    - SCAD - cases -- C to V, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-31)
    - SCAD - cases -- C to V, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-31)
    - SCAD - cases -- B to S, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-31)
    - SCAD - cases -- S, 1984; F-84-1-7-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-31)
  - Senate Committee on Undergraduate Studies (SCUS), 1971 - 1986; F-84-1-8; 3.76 m of textual records
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 18 - July 5, 1971, F-84-1-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-32)
      Pending Review
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 13, 1971, F-84-1-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-32)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 4-28, 1971, F-84-1-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-32)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 15, 1971, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-32)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 15, 1971, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-32)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 3. Nov. 15, 1971, vol. 3, F-84-1-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 84-32)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 29-30, 1971, F-84-1-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 84-33)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 6-20, 1971, F-84-1-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 84-33)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 13 - May 29, 1972, F-84-1-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 84-33)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. July 10, 1972, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 84-33)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. July 10, 1972, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 84-33)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 17 - Sept. 21, 1972, F-84-1-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 84-34)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 9, 1972, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 84-34)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 9, 1972, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 84-34)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 14-21, 1972, F-84-1-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 84-34)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 7, 1972, F-84-1-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 84-34)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Feb. 6, 1973, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 84-35)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Feb. 6, 1973, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-18 (Archival box - standard 84-35)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 13, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-19 (Archival box - standard 84-35)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 20, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-20 (Archival box - standard 84-35)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 20 - Apr. 3, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-21 (Archival box - standard 84-35)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 10-17, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-22 (Archival box - standard 84-36)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 21-28, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-23 (Archival box - standard 84-36)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 18-25, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-24 (Archival box - standard 84-36)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 25, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-25 (Archival box - standard 84-36)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 9, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-26 (Archival box - standard 84-36)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 23, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-27 (Archival box - standard 84-37)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 6, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-28 (Archival box - standard 84-37)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 13-20, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-29 (Archival box - standard 84-37)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 20, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-30 (Archival box - standard 84-37)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 18, 1973, F-84-1-8-0-31 (Archival box - standard 84-37)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 15, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-32 (Archival box - standard 84-38)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 26 - Mar. 12, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-33 (Archival box - standard 84-38)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 26 - Apr. 2, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-34 (Archival box - standard 84-38)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 9, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-35 (Archival box - standard 84-38)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 14 - June 4, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-36 (Archival box - standard 84-38)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 11, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-37 (Archival box - standard 84-39)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 25 - July 16, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-38 (Archival box - standard 84-39)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 23-30, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-39 (Archival box - standard 84-39)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 10-17, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-40 (Archival box - standard 84-39)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 24 - Oct. 8, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-41 (Archival box - standard 84-39)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 15, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-42 (Archival box - standard 84-40)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 22-29, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-43 (Archival box - standard 84-40)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 5, 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-44 (Archival box - standard 84-40)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 5, 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-45 (Archival box - standard 84-40)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 12, 1974, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-46 (Archival box - standard 84-40)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 12, 1974, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-47 (Archival box - standard 84-40)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 3-17, 1974, F-84-1-8-0-48 (Archival box - standard 84-41)
    - SCUS - correspondence, 1975; F-84-1-8-0-49 (Archival box - standard 84-41)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 14 - Feb. 11, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-50 (Archival box - standard 84-41)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 7-18, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-51 (Archival box - standard 84-41)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 25 - Apr. 1, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-52 (Archival box - standard 84-41)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 22, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-53 (Archival box - standard 84-42)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 20, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-54 (Archival box - standard 84-42)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 17 - Aug. 26, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-55 (Archival box - standard 84-42)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 23 - Oct. 14. 1975, F-84-1-8-0-56 (Archival box - standard 84-42)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 4, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-57 (Archival box - standard 84-42)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 12, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-58 (Archival box - standard 84-43)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 9-12, 1975, F-84-1-8-0-59 (Archival box - standard 84-43)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 27 - Feb. 10, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-60 (Archival box - standard 84-43)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 9 - May 12, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-61 (Archival box - standard 84-43)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 18 - June 15, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-62 (Archival box - standard 84-43)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 13, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-63 (Archival box - standard 84-44)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 14 - Oct. 26, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-64 (Archival box - standard 84-44)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 9-16, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-65 (Archival box - standard 84-44)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 23 - Dec. 7, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-66 (Archival box - standard 84-44)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 14, 1976, F-84-1-8-0-67 (Archival box - standard 84-44)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 1 - Mar. 8, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-68 (Archival box - standard 84-45)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 15-29, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-69 (Archival box - standard 84-45)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 5-26, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-70 (Archival box - standard 84-45)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 10 - June 14, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-71 (Archival box - standard 84-45)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 21 - July 12, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-72 (Archival box - standard 84-45)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 13-27, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-73 (Archival box - standard 84-45)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 18, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-74 (Archival box - standard 84-46)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov.1-8, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-75 (Archival box - standard 84-46)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 15, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-76 (Archival box - standard 84-46)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 22, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-77 (Archival box - standard 84-46)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 29, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-78 (Archival box - standard 84-46)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 13-22, 1977, F-84-1-8-0-79 (Archival box - standard 84-46)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Jan. 10, 1978, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-80 (Archival box - standard 84-47)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Jan. 10, 1978, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-81 (Archival box - standard 84-47)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 21, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-82 (Archival box - standard 84-47)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 7, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-83 (Archival box - standard 84-47)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 21, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-84 (Archival box - standard 84-47)
    - SCUS - administrative material, 1975 - 1978; F-84-1-8-0-85 (Archival box - standard 84-47)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 4-18, 1978, 1977 - 1978; F-84-1-8-0-86 (Archival box - standard 84-48)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 2. 1978, F-84-1-8-0-87 (Archival box - standard 84-48)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 9, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-88 (Archival box - standard 84-48)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 23 - June 20, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-89 (Archival box - standard 84-48)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 15, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-90 (Archival box - standard 84-48)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 24 - Oct. 10, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-91 (Archival box - standard 84-49)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 24, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-92 (Archival box - standard 84-49)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 7, 1978, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-93 (Archival box - standard 84-49)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 7, 1978, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-94 (Archival box - standard 84-49)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 14, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-95 (Archival box - standard 84-49)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 21 - Dec. 5, 1978, F-84-1-8-0-96 (Archival box - standard 84-49)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 30 - Apr. 10, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-97 (Archival box - standard 84-50)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 15-29, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-98 (Archival box - standard 84-50)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 12 - Aug. 7, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-99 (Archival box - standard 84-50)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 11, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-100 (Archival box - standard 84-50)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Spet. 25, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-101 (Archival box - standard 84-50)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 9, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-102 (Archival box - standard 84-51)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 30, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-103 (Archival box - standard 84-51)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 6, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-104 (Archival box - standard 84-51)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 13, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-105 (Archival box - standard 84-51)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 27 - Dec. 18, 1979, F-84-1-8-0-106 (Archival box - standard 84-51)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 12-26, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-107 (Archival box - standard 84-52)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 11-25, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-108 (Archival box - standard 84-52)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 2 - June 3, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-109 (Archival box - standard 84-52)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jun 18, 1970, 1980; F-84-1-8-0-110 (Archival box - standard 84-52)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Aug. 5, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-111 (Archival box - standard 84-52)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 9-16, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-112 (Archival box - standard 84-52)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 23 - Oct. 21, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-113 (Archival box - standard 84-53)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 4-5, 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-114 (Archival box - standard 84-53)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 4-5, 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-115 (Archival box - standard 84-53)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 1. Nov. 25, 1980, vol. 1, F-84-1-8-0-116 (Archival box - standard 84-53)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers, vol. 2. Nov. 25, 1980, vol. 2, F-84-1-8-0-117 (Archival box - standard 84-53)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 2-16, 1980, F-84-1-8-0-118 (Archival box - standard 84-53)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 13, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-119 (Archival box - standard 84-54)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 20-27, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-120 (Archival box - standard 84-54)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 10 - Mar. 10, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-121 (Archival box - standard 84-54)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 24, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-122 (Archival box - standard 84-54)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 7 - May 19, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-123 (Archival box - standard 84-54)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 9 - July 28, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-124 (Archival box - standard 84-54)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 28, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-125 (Archival box - standard 84-55)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 6-28, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-126 (Archival box - standard 84-55)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 3, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-127 (Archival box - standard 84-55)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 17, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-128 (Archival box - standard 84-55)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 1, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-129 (Archival box - standard 84-55)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 8, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-130 (Archival box - standard 84-56)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 15, 1981, F-84-1-8-0-131 (Archival box - standard 84-56)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 12 - Feb. 23, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-132 (Archival box - standard 84-56)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 9-30, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-133 (Archival box - standard 84-56)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 4, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-134 (Archival box - standard 84-56)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. June 1-29, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-135 (Archival box - standard 84-56)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. 14 - Oct. 5, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-136 (Archival box - standard 84-57)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 2, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-137 (Archival box - standard 84-57)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 9, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-138 (Archival box - standard 84-57)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 16, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-139 (Archival box - standard 84-57)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 30, 1982, F-84-1-8-0-140 (Archival box - standard 84-57)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 15, 1982 - Jan. 25, 1983, 1982 - 1983; F-84-1-8-0-141 (Archival box - standard 84-57)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Mar. 8 - May 13, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-142 (Archival box - standard 84-58)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 17, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-143 (Archival box - standard 84-58)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 26 - Sept. 20, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-144 (Archival box - standard 84-58)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 4-18, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-145 (Archival box - standard 84-58)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 1, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-146 (Archival box - standard 84-58)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 8, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-147 (Archival box - standard 84-59)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 15, 1983, F-84-1-8-0-148 (Archival box - standard 84-59)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 13, 1983 - Jan. 27, 1984, 1983 - 1984; F-84-1-8-0-149 (Archival box - standard 84-59)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 7 - Mar. 20, 1984, F-84-1-8-0-150 (Archival box - standard 84-59)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Apr. 24, 1984, F-84-1-8-0-151 (Archival box - standard 84-59)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 16, 1984, F-84-1-8-0-152 (Archival box - standard 84-59)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 13, 1984, F-84-1-8-0-153 (Archival box - standard 84-60)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 15, 1985, F-84-1-8-0-154 (Archival box - standard 84-60)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. 19 - Apr. 30, 1985, F-84-1-8-0-155 (Archival box - standard 84-60)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. July 23, 1985, F-84-1-8-0-156 (Archival box - standard 84-60)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 15-29, 1985, F-84-1-8-0-157 (Archival box - standard 84-60)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Nov. 26, 1985, F-84-1-8-0-158 (Archival box - standard 84-60)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Dec. 10, 1985, F-84-1-8-0-159 (Archival box - standard 84-61)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Jan. 21 - May 13, 1986, F-84-1-8-0-160 (Archival box - standard 84-61)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. May 27 - Sept. 30, 1986, F-84-1-8-0-161 (Archival box - standard 84-61)
    - SCUS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. 14, 1986, F-84-1-8-0-162 (Archival box - standard 84-61)
  - Senate Committee on Graduate Studies (SCGS), 1966 - 1986; F-84-1-9; 4.82 m of textual records
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. May - Dec. 1966, F-84-1-9-0-1 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - July 1967, F-84-1-9-0-2 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Sept. - Nov. 1967, F-84-1-9-0-3 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Feb. - May 1968, F-84-1-9-0-4 (Archival box - standard 84-62)
    - SCGS - agendas, minutes and papers. Oct. - Dec. 1968, F-84-1-9-0-5 (Archival box - standard 84-62)